ADEMOLA ADEWUMI

Full-stack Developer

- ? 10 Makinde St., Alausa, Ikeja, Nigeria
- □ ademolaadewumi01@gmail.com
 - +2348139340166
 - www.ademola.website

MATCHING COMPETENCIES

PROBLEM SOLVING

Problem-solving is a passion of mine and something I do for fun in my free time. I love puzzles, optimization, and critical thinking and I hone these skills in coding, bouldering, language-learning, gaming, and teaching.

ACCOUNTABILITY

Following-up, taking notes, organizing, and planning are skills that I have developed over many years as a professional. I am known for taking the lead through uncertain territory, acquiring resources, and ensuring proper accounting of time, objectives, and resources.

BROAD EXPERIENCE

Experiences as a client and, a leader and a follower, a freelancer and an employee, have instilled the drive and background to understand all aspects of a project as well as the ability to communicate these aspects to anyone involved.

WHY ME

As a full-stack developer with experience in web and mobile app development, I have a background that is relevant to all stakeholders, provides me unique insights, the ability to fully understand a project, and work well in a team. My experiences with the MERN stack have given me the tools to build exciting, responsive, and lightning-fast apps. Breaking down complex topics into digestible components is second nature to me and I have gone through the grind of extensive learning again and again.

Education/Courses

THE COMPLETE JUNIOR TO SENIOR DEVELOPER ROADMAP, UDEMY

08/2020 - present

Flutter App Development, UDEMY

05/2020 - present

THE COMPLETE WEB DEVELOPER IN 2019,

UDEMY

01/2019 - 06/2020

Udemy- Andrei Neagoie

B.Sc Geology and Mineral Science,

University of Ilorin 2014 – 2018

EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Developer, FREELANCE

09/2019 - present

As a freelance developer, I designed and built several different apps of interest for potential use.

IT Officer, *BOTOSOFT TECHNOLOGY* 03/2020 – 05/2020

- Online verification of Identity
- Production of chip encoded cards
- Installation and verification of software

Teacher, HANEEF COLLEGE

2018 – 2019

(NYSC)

Factory Supervisor, DY CONNECT

2018 - 2019 (NYSC)

Skills

HTML, CSS/SCSS, JAVASCRIPT, REST/JSON, NODE/EXPRESS.JS, BOOSTRAP, REACT.JS/REDUX, AWS, FLUTTER, FIREBASE, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, TYPESCRIPT, PYTHON

References

Available on request.